import { Category } from 'src/app/interfaces/category.interface';

export default {
  name: 'Урок от 28го февраля',
  cards: [{
    question: 'to assume',
    answer: 'предполагать',
  }, {
    question: 'express',
    answer: 'выражать',
  }, {
    question: 'concern',
    answer: 'беспокойство',
  }, {
    question: 'evidence',
    answer: 'доказательство',
  }, {
    question: 'according to',
    answer: 'согласно с',
  }, {
    question: 'certain',
    answer: 'определенный',
  }, {
    question: 'dimension',
    answer: 'измерение',
  }, {
    question: 'anxious (энкшиос)',
    answer: 'тревожный',
  }, {
    question: 'take part',
    answer: 'принимать участие',
  }, {
    question: 'overall',
    answer: ' в общем',
  }, {
    question: 'activities',
    answer: 'занятие',
  }, {
    question: 'pastime',
    answer: 'времяпрепровождение',
  }, {
    question: 'yet again',
    answer: 'опять же',
  }, {
    question: 'embankment',
    answer: 'набережная',
  },
  ],
} as Category;
